# Kyle Keilson



### **About**

Experienced Network and Systems Engineer with a demonstrated history of working in the information technology and services industry. Skilled in macOS, Network Technologies, Microsoft Office 365, Bash, and strong contributor in documentation. Strong information technology professional with a Bachelor of Science (B.S.) focused in Network Engineering and and Security from DePaul University.

#### Contact

www.keilson.org

Sarasota, FL



## **Experience**

Cloud Systems Engineer Manager, macOS Technology and Help Desk Ringling College of Art and Design, Sarasota, FL 2021-Present 2019-2021

- Maintain virtual machines and ESXi Hosts using VMware VCenter
- Managed installation, maintenance, and troubleshooting of Apple desktop and laptops
- Designed and maintained MDM environment for 500+ devices
- Managed Cisco UCS blade and Dell PowerEdge servers
- Serve as Adobe representative for college

## Systems Engineer / Team Lead SouthTech Solutions, Sarasota, FL

2017-2019

- Monitor daily goals and assisted team members with reaching those goals, including case resolution and troubleshooting assistance
- Installed on premise equipment including BDRs, firewalls, routers, switches, access points, and servers

#### Technology Support Specialist Technology Support Center Associate Analyst DePaul University, Chicago, IL

2015-2017

- ☑ Create, maintain and escalate tickets via PeopleSoft CRM system to meet or exceed our service level agreements (SLA)
- Worked on a team to develop Single Sign-On (RADIUS) solution for wireless customers
- ☑ Diagnose, troubleshoot, research, resolve and document Tier II hardware, software, networking, authentication, and IP telephony issues for internal and external customers

## গ্রি

### **Education**

DePaul University, Chicago, IL Bachelor of Science in Network Technology 2009-2014

## **Skills/Certifications**

CCNA	macOS	VLANs
Bash	Windows	DHCP/DNS
Cisco IOS	JAMF Pro	VMware VCenter